Vishal Chandra Chapa

Manchester, India, +44 7435 378497, vishc264@gmail.com

LINKEDIN	https://www.linkedin.com/in/vishal-chandra-chapa-1548871ab/	
PROFILE	I am a Software Engineer specializing in Full Stack Development, Support Engineering, and Data Science. I bring a blend of technical expertise and strategic vision to my work. I am a certified Frontend Developer, with Level-certification in Data Science and Level-2 certification by NCFE. My strong interpersonal and leadership skills complement my technical abilities, positioning me as an ideal candidate for your organization. With experience in software analysis, maintenance, and management, I hold both MSc and Bachelor degrees.	
EMPLOYMENT HISTORY		
Jun 2024 — Present	Full Stack Software Developer, Co	Hybrid Working de Institute Environmen
	As a Junior Full Stack Software Development, gaining developing with HTML, CSS, BootStrap framework, JavaScript, Python and Django.	
Feb 2024 — May 2024	Support Engineer, GAO Tek Inc.	Hybrid Working Environmen
	Worked as a Support Engineer delivering exceptional user interface support by promptly addressing user querie and technical issues. This involves troubleshooting UI-related solutions, providing clear and concise instructions and ensuring seamless user experiences. Collaborating with senior developers and UX/UI designers with expertising in wordpress. Overall, with GAO Tek Inc, I have contributed UI functionality, Team-Collaboration Documentation, Analysing and Project Management.	
May 2022 — Jan 2024	Manager, Best One Express	
	I have identified potential new clients and markets, improved service for existing customers through analysing. also managed risks, train, Hire and mentor team members.	
Sep 2022 — Mar 2023	Data Analyst, Orcalo Hybrid Work Environm	
	I am Responsible for developing, decoded and encoded software web applications. maintained and keeping up to date with data systems, collaborated with multiple teams to identified process improvements and develop strategies. Utilised statistical tools for data analysis, generated reports for management and propose system analysis to enhance user-reach.	
EDUCATION		
Sep 2021 — Jun 2023	Master of Science, Anglia Ruskin University Cambridge	
Jun 2015 — Oct 2020	Bachelor of Technology, Mallareddy College of Engineering and Technology Hyderabad	
SKILLS	JavaScript (Programming Language)	Node.js
	Python (Programming Language)	BootStrap (framework) HyperText Markup Language (HTML)
	Django (Web Framework)	(HTML)
	User Experience Design (UX)	Project Management
	React.js	Data Analysis
LANGUAGES	English	Hindi

LANGUAGES English Hindi